紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   章魚埃克斯
時間軸   大蔥
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第四集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
我還能感覺到他的手推在我后背上
I can still feel his hand on my back.
凱茜  他已經不在了
Cathy, he's gone.
比爾·謝潑德已經買通了她
Bill Shepherd got to her.
她會作證的
She's going to testify.
弗萊德·安博格叫我來見你
Fred Amburg asked me to meet you.
弗萊德也叫我來見你
Well, Fred asked me to meet you
我是你的機會
I am your chance.
除了科爾議員  他還見誰了嗎
And besides Congressman Cole, has he met with anyone?
還有湯姆·漢默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
或許你該去跟他
Perhaps you should be the one on him.
他沒有解雇我  是我主動辭職的
He didn't fire me. I resigned.
我與白宮中的某些人
I had some fundamental differences of opinion
基本理念不合
with certain people in the White House.
比如誰  總統嗎
Like who? The president?
副總統  弗蘭克·安德伍德
The vice president, Frank Underwood.
你有湯姆·耶茨的消息嗎  凱爾茜
Have you heard from Tom Yates, Kelsey?
-沒有  -你跟他挺好的  是吧
- No. - You were friendly with him, right?
他在布拉格周邊用過信用卡
He's been using his credit card in and around Prague.
那太好了
I'm glad to hear it.
簡  你怎么能這么對我
Jane, how could you do this to me?
是克萊爾嗎
Is this Claire?
你是為了她嗎
Are you doing this for her?
一旦決定已下  你就逃不掉了
Once the decision is made, you can't escape.
或許今天不會
Maybe it won't happen today,
但是  恐怕總有那一天
but someday, I'm afraid.
走著瞧吧  是吧
Well, we'll see. Will we?
天吶
Oh, my God.
什么時候的事
When did it happen?
我上次跟她談話時
The last conversation I had with her,
她還在說她的新工作
she was talking about her new job
以及那本該是多么好的機會
and what a great opportunity it was going to be.
兄弟姐妹  我如今把一件奧秘的事告訴你們
Brothers and sisters, behold, I tell you a mystery.
歌林多前書15:50
我們不是都要睡覺
We shall not all fall asleep,
乃是都要改變
but we will all be changed
就在眨眼之間  號筒末次吹響的時候
in an instant, in the blink of an eye, at the last trumpet.
因號筒要響
For the trumpet will sound
死人要復活成為不朽壞的
and the dead will be raised incorruptible,
我們也要改變
and we shall be changed.
全能的主啊
Almighty God,
您賜予您仆人的福愛  求您莫要忘了
remember the mercy with which you graced your humble servant.
我們祈禱  您恩賜她進入圣徒的福地
Receive her, we pray, into the mansions of the saints.
我們的姐妹安息天國時
As we prepare our sister's final resting,
愿主也垂憐她哀悼的親人
look also with love on those who mourn
賜他們以安寧
and give them comfort in their loss.
我主耶穌保佑  阿門
Grant this through Christ, our Lord, Amen.
阿門
Amen.
-總統女士  能搭您的車嗎  -當然
- Madam President, can I ride with you? - Of course.
他找過你了嗎
Has he approached you?
誰
Who?
佩特羅夫
Petrov.
他不是剛到嗎
Didn't he just arrive?
敘利亞問題的談判破裂了  他來干什么
If the talks on Syria have broken down, what's he doing here?
不是好事就是壞事
It's either a good thing or a bad thing.
那是好是壞
Well, which is it?
總統女士
Madam President?
他喜歡凱茜
He was fond of Cathy.
我需要知道  你不會妨礙我處理...
I need to know that you won't stand in the way of my handling...
馬克  結束了
Mark. It's done.
你贏了
You won.
給你看是必要的
It was necessary to show you,
但我并不想這樣
but not what I wanted.
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你害了我也害了自己  這得怪你
You did that to both of us. You did it.
你把我卷進來  害我有牽連
You involved me, you implicated me.
-你把他丟在我房子里  -馬克  夠了
- You left him in my house. - Mark, that's enough.
都不重要了
It doesn't matter anymore.
斯坦  請節哀順變
Stan, my deepest condolences.
這是凱茜的弟弟亨特  從尤金趕過來的
This is Cathy's brother Hunter. He flew in from Eugene.
就在萊恩縣外
Just outside Lane County.
那里的鄉景很美
Beautiful country out there.
我本來也打算出來走走
I was planning to come out anyway.
六號就是斯坦的生日了
Stan's birthday is on the sixth.
凱茜和我
Cathy and I have been...
忙活了幾個月了
back and forth for months.
您喪失至親  我非常難過
I'm so sorry for your loss.
道格  這位是凱茜的弟弟亨特
Doug, this is Cathy's brother Hunter.
你認識斯坦
And you've met Stan.
-當然  -謝謝你過來
- Of course. - Thank you for coming.
我想道格大概是與凱茜相處最久的了
Doug, I think, spent more time with Cathy than anyone.
真是太可惜了
She didn't deserve this.
說實話  我都覺得有些不真實
Honestly, it doesn't seem real.
失陪一下好嗎
Would you excuse me?
她什么時候過世的
What time did she die?
我不...
I don't...
抱歉  我知道這么問不合適  我只是
Sorry, I know it's a weird question. I just...
我那天突然有所感應
I had one of those feelings that day.
5點43分吧
5:43, I think.
是啊  差不多就是那時候
Yeah, right around then.
總統先生
Mr. President.
安德伍德總統
President Underwood.
杜蘭特國務卿是來自上一個時代的人
Secretary Durant was from a time that's passed.
克林頓政府駐聯合國大使
奧巴馬政府駐中東特使
克林頓政府國務卿
霍爾布魯克  奧爾布賴特
Holbrooke, Albright...
他們知道先觥籌交錯  推杯換盞一番
They knew how to have a good meal and some friendly conversation
再去廝殺那些外交問題
before diplomacy got ugly.
失去了她  確實是不復當年了
It certainly won't be the same without her.
我聽說他們把你拴得很緊
I hear they have you on a short leash.
你怎么能容忍這種事呢  總統女士
How could you let that happen, Madam President?
如今危機又近在眼前
Now, when we're only moments away from crisis.
在某些文化中
You know, in some cultures
人們還會真正紀念死者
it occurs to them to actually honor the dead.
馬達加斯加人每過七年
Every seven years the Malagasy people
會挖出遺骨  裹上衣服
exhume the bones, wrapping them in cloth,
然后和它們一起跳舞
so they can dance with the bodies.
這座城市又是如何面對的呢
How does this town rise to the occasion?
他們的腦袋下面就跟有彈簧似的
It's like their heads are on a swivel.
那東西叫什么來著
Yeah. What do you call those things?
搖頭娃娃
Bobble heads?
太可怕了
Terrifying.
不  別去  隨她去吧
No, don't... Let her be.
是你想讓她有總統的樣兒
You wanted her to play the part.
看吧
Voilà.
-這不是了嗎  -總統太好說話了
- The President. - the President is too agreeable.
你對她做了什么
What did you do to her?
比起現在這一套  我更相信她的輕蔑
I trust her contempt more than whatever this is.
親愛的  我知道你的能耐
Love, I know what you're capable of.
國防情報局認為有超過十萬名俄軍士兵
DIA believes there are over 100,000 Russian troops
-正在向邊境進軍  -你聯系布加耶夫了嗎
- on their way to the border. - Did you find Bugayev?
幾分鐘之前  他的副手向我保證
As of a few minutes ago, his second in command assured me
克里姆林宮
that was the last contact
將不會再與我們聯系
we would have from anyone at the Kremlin.
除了他
Except for him.
他請求和總統進行私下會晤
He's requesting a private meeting with the President.
-好啊  -該死的
- Sure. - God damn it.
-總統先生  -副總統先生
- Mr. President. - Mr. Vice President.
您見過西格森國務卿
You know Secretary Siegerson.
-當然  -見到您很高興
- Yes. Of course. - So good to see you.
總統女士  打擾一下
Madam President, excuse me.
好的  失陪一下
Oh, yes. Excuse me a moment.
當然
Of course.
凱茜對我很好
Cathy was kind to me.
她是大家的榜樣  通情達理  精于業務
A role model. Sensible, shrewd.
法語很流利
Fluent in French.
愿她安息
Repose en paix.
我知道現在說不合適  但是
I know it's not the place, but...
眼下的情況太不正常了
this isn't normal, what's going on.
我接受這個職位的時候
When I accepted my position,
是為了協助您推進您的計劃
it was to work with you and your agenda,
而不是
not...
本屆內閣的某些
Certain members of our Cabinet
與國安部事務有關的人
in positions related to National Security
已經就敘利亞問題進行了多次密會
have had several secret meetings regarding Syria.
佩特羅夫總統已經知道
President Petrov has become aware
他們計劃排遣雇傭兵進入該地區的事
of their plans for sending private contractors to the region.
女士
Ma'am...
五角大樓一些高層
there are officials in the Pentagon,
克里姆林宮里也有人非常希望能避免一場
people at the Kremlin, who would very much like to prevent
-代理人戰爭  -諾拉  謝謝你的坦誠
- a proxy war... - Nora, I appreciate your candor,
但馬克會處理的
but Mark has this.
女士  內閣都成了他的了
Ma'am, the Cabinet is his.
他知道我們該怎么做
He knows what we need to do.
我之所以懷疑你想競爭議長  是因為
What makes me suspect you're vying for speaker is
盡管領跑選手天天換
the frontrunners change day to day,
但是大家心中的次選始終沒變過
but everybody's second choice remains the same.
-就是你  -布雷特  難道你會讓賢
- You. - Brett, are you saying you wouldn't do it,
拒絕黨內征召嗎
if the party asked?
這說明黨還沒昏了頭  分得清好壞
If the party knew what was good for them.
這位是道格拉斯·斯坦普  他現在是顧問
This is Douglas Stamper. He's coming on as a consultant.
大家都認識
We've met.
弗蘭西斯當黨鞭時認識的約拿
Jonah, back when Francis was whip,
而你  當年還只是端咖啡的小廝
and you, back when you were getting us coffee.
我倒確實想知道  議員先生
I do wonder how he'd feel with some
對他署名的一些法案到底有什么看法
of the legislation the good congressman is putting his name on.
三權分立是憲法之本
Constitution was built on checks and balances.
還有人民的意愿
And the people's will.
總統是誰并不重要
It's not about who the President is.
重要的是政府變成了什么樣
It's about what the office has become.
先生們  容我失陪一下
Gentlemen, if you'll excuse me for a minute,
我答應了布雷特介紹些溫和派民主黨議員給他認識
I promised Brett here I'd introduce him to a blue dog Democrat,
如果我找得到的話
assuming I can find one.
沒想到還能再見到他
I never thought I'd see him again.
他去復健了
He was in rehab.
又開始戒酒了
And is back in the program.
那些指控都撤銷了
Those charges were dropped,
但還有一樁案子追著他呢
but he's still got a case chasing him.
要我猜  那案子怕是沖著總統去的
If anything, my bet is that case is chasing the President.
佩特羅夫離開大廳了
Petrov is no longer in the main room.
西格森國務卿還和戴維斯女士在一起
Secretary Siegerson is still with Ms. Davis,
副總統正要出去
while the vice president's exiting.
國土安全部部長的卡弗蒂
And Homeland Secretary Cafferty
剛和總統密語了好一陣子
was just whispering with the President.
而道格·斯坦普在和助理局長格林說話
As for Doug Stamper, he's with Assistant Director Green.
我想知道當時誰和杜蘭特在一起
I want to know who Durant was with,
什么時間去了哪  直到她被宣布死亡
when and where, leading up to the moment she was pronounced dead.
如果我去打聽的話
If I start asking around...
只會問來更多問題
Questions bring more questions.
-這是公開調查嗎  -不是
- Is this an open investigation? - No.
不過我會提醒著點和我共事的探員
But for any agent I work with, I'll be the red flag.
道格  我知道得越多  對你我就越有利
Doug, the more I know, the better it is for both of us.
你相信我嗎
You trust me?
你總是堅持到底
You've always followed through.
那就聽我的
Then do as I say.
你發現了什么
But what did you find?
他招了嗎
Is he talking?
好的  有什么新情況就向我匯報
All right. Get back to me when you know anything more.
無論什么時候
Day or night.
有什么事嗎
Is everything okay?
是關于湯姆·耶茨的
That was about Tom Yates.
他的信用卡最近發生了一筆消費
There's been a recent charge on his credit card.
就在布拉格的馬克大酒店
The Grand Mark in Prague,
只不過并不是湯姆
except it wasn't Tom.
他沒進行那筆消費  其他的也不是他
He didn't make the charge. Or any of the others.
-有人偷了他的  -他的身份
- Somebody stole his... - His identity.
我們現在不知道真正的湯姆·耶茨去了哪
As of now, we have no idea where the real Tom Yates has been.
但愿他沒事
Well, I hope he's safe.
不管他在哪
Wherever he is.
我也是
Me too.
1945年產的木桐·羅斯柴爾德
1945 Mouton-Rothschild.
V標
"V" Label.
羅斯柴爾德訂了這瓶酒  來慶祝盟軍
Rothschild commissioned it to celebrate the Allied victory
在偉大衛國戰爭中的勝利
in the Great Patriotic War.
你是指第二次世界大戰
You mean World War II.
不知道她是想留著慶祝什么
I wonder what she was saving this for.
要不要嘗嘗
Should we?
拜托  你心底里總還有點玩心吧
Come on. There must be some mischief in you somewhere.
你反對嗎
Do you object?
我沒資格
Not my place.
那你有什么資格
And where exactly is your place?
我明確要求和你們總統會面
I specifically asked to meet with the President.
這里肯定有個開瓶器吧
There must be a corkscrew somewhere, hmm?
她藏了這么多酒  怎么可能沒有開瓶器呢
She wouldn't keep these bottles in here without one.
-說到敘利亞  總統先生  -請先等等
- When it comes to Syria, Mr. President... - A moment, please.
先生
Sir...
我們唯一的目標就是保持穩定
our only goal is stability,
為敘利亞人民謀求和平  繁榮
peace, prosperity for the Syrian people.
我們得重新接觸  重開談判
We need to re-engage. We need to re-start talks...
談判
Talks?
就知道談
Talk, talk, talk.
然后一轉臉就去和奈克西斯幕后交易
While you're busy making side deals with Nexis
還有你們那群共和黨朋友
and the rest of your Republican friends.
謝潑德家族
The Shepherds.
他們才是你的主子  是不是
That is who you really work for, isn't it?
我們可以凍結資產
We can freeze assets,
重新啟動制裁
put sanctions back into place.
這會兒
Must be about...
大馬士革是晚上七點半
7:30 at night in Damascus.
如果我們無所作為
If we do nothing,
到天亮  我們兩軍的遭遇戰就會開始
by dawn, skirmishes between our troops and yours will begin.
等到俄軍打死幾個你們美軍士兵
And once Russian soldiers start killing American soldiers,
亂局就會繼續擴大
the chaos will continue.
或者
Or...
我們現在就鋪開敘利亞地圖
we can pull out a map of Syria, right here, right now.
而你和我  亮出帝國主義者的本色
And you and I, like the imperialists we are,
瓜分各自的利益吧
can decide who gets what.
好嗎
Shall we?
我去和總統談談
I'll speak to the President.
誰能拍板
Whoever decides...
你就找誰說去吧
is who you should speak to.
真是可惜
What a shame.
太可惜了
我和道格談過了  他問了我
I talked to Doug. He asked me,
一開始我還以為他是想掩蓋
and at first I thought he was just covering his tracks,
他與國務卿之死的瓜葛  但是
as far as the Secretary's death, but...
現在我也不知道
Now I wonder...
他的問題是何用意了
the nature of his questions.
女士  我打了幾個電話
Ma'am, I've made some calls.
有些細節對不上
There are some inconsistencies.
她離家的時間  死亡的地點
When she left her house. Where she died.
-等等  什么意思  -我并不是說是假的
- Wait, what are you telling me? - I'm not saying it isn't true...
你等等  慢點說
Just a second, back up.
我只是說還很難確定
It's just hard to be certain is all I'm saying.
-我要你去找到他  -我不能再和他說話了
- I'd like you to go find him. - I can't talk to him again.
我是擔心他會起疑
My fear is he'll become suspicious.
他知道我一向聽話
He knows me as someone who does what he's told.
我不明白  如果不是他  那么
I don't understand, If it's not him, then...
她到底是怎么死的
how did she die, for God's sake?
女士
Ma'am...
我也不知道
I don't know.
謝潑德先生希望你隨時匯報最新情況
Mr. Shepherd would like to be kept informed in real time.
我都有數
It's under control.
那你就更應該跟我們通氣了
Then it shouldn't be a problem to keep us included.
你知道我認識謝潑德家多少年了嗎
Do you understand how long I've known the Shepherds?
不管你和佩特羅夫談什么  都得要他點頭
Whatever you discussed with Petrov needs to be run by him.
我給你上一課  格雷森先生
Let me enlighten you about something, Mr. Grayson.
我和比爾·謝潑德
I do not need you to convey
用不著你在中間傳話  明白了嗎
a message between me and Bill Shepherd, okay?
那更好  只要您  請原諒我唐突
Well, that's preferable, as long as, and forgive me,
不背著他擅自決定敘利亞的事
you make no decisions when it comes to Syria without his say-so.
-步子別邁得太大  先生  -到此為止
- Don't get over your skis, sir. - We're done here.
-我不認為  -副總統說了  到此為止
- I don't think... - The vice president says we are done.
道格·斯坦普
Doug Stamper.
琳達  你還好嗎
Linda. How are you?
-葬禮你沒去  -我去遲了
- You weren't at the funeral. - I arrived late.
退出政壇了吧
Out of politics, I understand?
沃克總統給我安排了很好的去處
President Walker made sure I had a soft landing.
我現在在科羅拉多一所大學
I'm at a university in Colorado,
是個山清水秀的好地方
where the water is fresh and the air is clean.
-聽起來很危險  -沒錯
- Sounds dangerous. - It is.
讓你頭腦太清醒
To think that clearly.
你還好嗎
How are you?
你看過什么了
What have you read?
關于你的嗎
About you?
差不多都看了
Most of it.
至少過去三個月的
The last three months of it.
你所謂的供詞
About your supposed confession.
既然你都看過了  我還有什么好補充的呢
What more could I possibly add that you haven't already read?
能看到的是一回事  真相又是一回事
There's what you read, and there's the truth.
我并不覺得羞愧
I'm not ashamed.
休養的時光讓我發現了真正的自我
The time away led me to finally realize who I am.
議員知道你的事嗎
Does the congressman know about you?
我是說  真的知道嗎
I mean... know.
有我的幫助  他會成為下一任眾院議長
With my help he's gonna be the next speaker of the House...
我和聯邦檢察官是法學院同學
I went to law school with the US Attorney.
她等夠了
She's tired of waiting.
她明天會簽發一張給你的傳票
She's issuing a subpoena with your name on it sometime tomorrow.
跟她說實話吧
Tell her what you know.
這樣你還有幸存的機會  道格
You have a chance to survive all this, Doug.
塔爾圖斯  是吧
Tartus, da?
但舍棄海岸其余的部分
But the rest of the coast...
我們承受得了嗎
can we afford to let it go?
再見
Goodbye.
能行
It could work.
佩特羅夫計劃把海軍基地
Petrov has plans to expand the Naval base
擴建到塔爾圖斯港
to the port of Tartus.
他支持敘利亞當局的唯一原因
The only reason he's propping up the regime
就是因為他們控制著海岸
is because they control the coast.
他需要港口
He needs the ports.
只要拿港口挾住他
Force him to fight for those
他就會對敘利亞其余地區放手
and he'll leave the rest of Syria alone.
馬克
Mark...
機會來了
the moment is here.
他人在這兒
He's here.
時機不等人啊
It can't wait.
我還是不明白
I still don't understand how
為什么條件還沒有談妥  就已經...
agreements which haven't even been finalized yet...
-不重要  他聽到風聲了  -誰透的風
- Doesn't matter. He got wind of it. - From who?
重點在于  他是個貪婪的
The point is, is he is a greedy...
王八蛋  沒錯
Motherfucker, yes.
貪婪的王八蛋總是會察覺
And greedy motherfuckers always find out.
他不達目的不罷休
He's relentless.
我在西北庫爾德人區待過兩年
I spent two years in the Kurdish northwest,
給東南叛軍賣過武器
outfitted rebels in the southeast.
我知道佩特羅夫能打的所有招數
I know every angle Petrov will keep in play.
他對對手的猶疑極其敏感
He has a sixth sense when it comes to hesitation.
如果你需要我參與...
If you need me to be in there...
你就是做不到  是不是
You just can't do it, can you?
-什么  -沒什么
- What? - Nothing.
-馬克  -你就是不肯放手信任別人
- Mark... - You just can't step back and trust.
我信任你  馬克
I trust you, Mark.
但是后座總統
But if the backseat president
想掌權  你就得坐到駕駛席上
is gonna take the wheel, you gotta drive.
你和我孤零零一個人是有原因的  簡
There's a reason you and I are alone in the world, Jane.
是  好的
Yes, of course.
-多久沒見了  -就好像一輩子
- How long? - A lifetime.
你搬到西部去了吧  能多陪陪兒子了
You moved out west, right? More time with your son.
只要他肯陪我
As much as he'll give me.
-他還喜歡斯坦...  -克萊爾
- And is he still enjoying Stan... - Claire.
總統女士
Madam President,
我們之間用不著來這套虛的
we don't need to exchange pleasantries.
我如今常想  另一種可能是什么樣子
These days I tend to think a lot about what might have been.
我想道歉
I'd like to apologize.
-為什么  -我最大的悔恨
- For what? - My one regret.
我應該去加夫尼的
I should've been there in Gaffney.
說真的
Honestly,
我心里一直放不下
it's been haunting me.
有件事該告訴他的
There was something he needed to know.
那是個錯誤
It was a mistake.
沒有讓弗蘭西斯當國務卿
Overlooking Francis for secretary of state.
-琳達  都過去了  -不對
- Linda, it's water under the bridge. - No.
不對
No.
如果沒有當初
If we hadn't,
可就說不準了
I don't know.
也許一切都會不一樣了
Maybe everything would have been different.
對誰而言呢
For who?
整個國家
This country.
當然  現在我也沒法對他說了
Obviously, there's no way for me to tell him that now.
但至少我還能對你說
The least I can do is tell you.
你不必這樣的
There is no need for that.
他那些罪行  你打算怎么撇清關系
How do you expect to separate yourself from his crimes?
雖然我們容忍政治變得如此腐敗
As corrupt as these politics we put up with have become...
但反對你的人怎么會不加以利用呢
how can the people against you not use it?
你以為你能清白脫身  克萊爾
You thought you got away with it all, Claire.
但結果還不一定呢
But that remains to be seen.
發生的一切  都是該發生的
Everything happens exactly as it should.
見到你很高興
Nice seeing you.
你在想什么呢
What are you up to?
我在想生死之事
I'm thinking about mortality.
我想今天好多人都在想這件事
I think a lot of us are doing that today.
一會兒要開個會
We're about to have a meeting.
我參與不了  維克多太了解我了
I can't be a part of it. Viktor knows me all too well.
有我呢
I'm on board.
我知道  克萊爾  我告訴馬克不必擔心
Claire, I see you. I told Mark not to worry about it.
但我感覺未必...
But I have an inkling that's not necessarily...
少說什么感覺吧  簡
Spare me your inkling, Jane.
這個交易是為了你好
This deal is for your own good.
是為了整個地區
It's about the whole region.
事關我們的存在  我們的權威
Our presence. Our authority.
重活交給馬克和瑪茜去干吧
Mark and Marcy can do the heavy lifting.
今天就幫我阻止戰爭吧
Help me prevent a war from happening today.
再有任何動蕩  所有人都輸
Any more instability and everybody loses.
幫我避免這種局面吧
Help me avert that.
我向你保證
I promise you...
我會逐漸瓦解比爾和安奈特·謝潑德的影響力
I will chip away at Bill and Annette Shepherd.
因為要想把他們徹底扳倒
Because the only way to truly take them down
就只能步步為營
is one piece at a time.
你認為凱茜到底發生什么了
What do you think really happened to Cathy?
好吧
Okay.
你大概是運氣好吧
I guess you got lucky then.
沒人運氣那么好
No one is that lucky.
總統愿意對海岸歸屬不持異議
the President is willing to leave the coast uncontested.
-塔爾圖斯港  -已經是我們的了
- Tartus... - That port is already ours.
你們可以繼續保留
And will remain so.
我們的軍力將遠離西海岸
We'll keep our forces away from the entire Western coast.
這樣你們就可以自由進出地中海
This will give you unfettered access to the Mediterranean.
-不行  -先生  第六艦隊已經出發了
- No. - Sir, the Sixth Fleet is en route.
-不行  -如果你想引發海軍對峙的話
- No. - If you want a naval standoff...
打住  咱們都不要裝了
No! Let's not pretend.
對你們而言真正重要的是從中取利...
What's really at stake here is your country lining its pockets and...
總統女士
Madam President,
總統先生
Mr. President,
-副總統要求我參會  -格雷森先生
- the vice president asked me to join. - Mr. Grayson...
我代表的是一家
On behalf of a company
-在中東有業務的公司  -你說什么
- with subsidiaries in the Middle East. - Excuse me.
我們希望談判結果能照顧到我方利益
We want to ensure that we're part of the solution.
這將向全世界發出信號  俄羅斯回來了
This will signal to the world that Russia is back.
-俄羅斯回來了  -副總統先生
- Russia's back? - Mr. Vice President,
正在談判的一些條件還需要進一步討論
there are terms being negotiated here that need to be discussed...
天啊
Christ!
要是杜蘭特國務卿還在
If Secretary Durant were here,
我們早就過了假模假式的環節
we'd be long past this posturing
-去解決真正問題了  -沒錯  區域和平
- and dealing with the real question. - Yes, peace in the region.
和平  不是吧
Peace? Really?
你想用和平來決定
You want to use peace to decide
誰來重建這個пиздеть
who will rebuild this pizdets?
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't understand what that means,
-總統先生  -意思是糞坑
- Mr. President. - That means clusterfuck.
先生  維持區域穩定對大家都有好處
Sir, stability in the region helps all of us.
你們想把西部給我  拿走東部
You want to give me the West and take the East?
真是第一次聽說
That's a first.
那么我的條件如下
So, here's what I want.
港口我們當然要
The ports, yes, of course.
但我還要求俄羅斯
But I also want Russian
獨占所有近海石油和天然氣開發
exclusivity on all offshore oil and gas exploration.
-這個得商量一下  -閉嘴吧你
- I think we need to wait. - Shut up.
我們不能進得去
We can't be in a position where we can get in,
卻不能把資源帶出來
and we can't get our resources out.
歷史留給我們的經驗  就是
If history has taught us anything, it's that
美國人總有辦法全身而退
the Americans always find a way to leave,
無論代價多大
no matter what it costs them.
那么
So...
有什么想法嗎  總統女士
thoughts, Madam President?
有話說嗎
Anything?
我同意副總統的看法
I concur with the vice president.
看來我們還有很多需要考慮
I believe we have much to consider.
示弱太累了
Playing incompetent is so exhausting.
這一份是總統今晚
Here's a copy of the President's remarks
在國務卿追悼會上的講話復本
for the secretary's memorial this evening.
我已經有一份了
I already have a copy.
這一份有她在車上做的修改
It includes the changes she made in the car.
好的  謝謝
Right. Thank you.
話說湯姆·耶茨真的失蹤了嗎
Is it true Tom Yates is missing?
看來是
I believe so.
他真的和白宮里的什么人有一腿嗎
Is it true he had an affair with somebody in the White House?
是你嗎
Was it you?
什么
Excuse me.
我會看一看的
I'll look through this.
謝謝
Thank you.
-我不喜歡撒謊的人  -我也是
- I don't like liars. - Me neither.
你為什么讓我以為...
Why would you let me believe...
你似乎想讓我為凱茜的死負責
It seemed like you wanted me to be the one responsible for Cathy.
這可能對你有幫助
That it might be useful to you somehow.
每次我想抽身  就會出什么意外
Every time I plan to quit, something happens.
弗蘭西斯一定對我很失望
Francis would certainly be disappointed in me.
不是好習慣
Terrible habit.
不過我戒酒時幫了我的忙
Helped me though when I quit drinking.
不要對聯邦檢察官開口  道格
Don't say anything to the US attorney, Doug.
她在和謝潑德家族合作
She's working with the Shepherds.
我今晚就赦免你
I pardon you tonight,
她手上你的任何把柄就是我的問題了
and anything else she has will be my problem.
我永遠都是你的問題
I'll always be a problem for you.
你還想要我怎樣  道格
What do you want from me, Doug?
現在籌碼都在你的手上
You're the one with all the leverage here.
科爾議員  我讓他跟我一起競選2020
Congressman Cole. I'll put him on my ticket 2020.
馬克一定會走人  我能肯定
Mark won't survive, I'm sure of it.
2024年  布雷特·科爾就是總統
2024, Brett Cole will be the President.
你就能重回白宮
And you will be back in the White House.
我們可以把他推上總統寶座
We can make him president,
就像我們幫弗蘭西斯那樣
just like we did with Francis.
和科爾搭檔的話就是正副不同黨了
Cole will mean a split ticket.
也許這正是我們國家最需要的呢
And that might be the very best thing for this country.
那你也得赦免弗蘭西斯
Pardon Francis as well.
那我就會被彈劾
If I do that, I could get impeached.
不會
No.
你總能活下來  你已經證明了這一點
You're a survivor. You've proven that much.
赦免他
Pardon him as well.
比爾絕對無法接受
Bill's gonna hate anything
跟克里姆林宮任何形式的合作
even approaching a partnership with the Kremlin.
記仇的是他妹妹
It's his sister who holds a grudge.
但你還是沒有選擇
But still, you have no choice.
以我的經驗  一旦混亂演變成了萬劫不復
I mean, in my experience, once the chaos tips into forever,
你也會一無所獲
you've got nothing.
而我們離萬劫不復就差一點了
And we're very close to forever.
她什么都沒說
And she said nothing.
你真的很在意  是不是
It really bothers you, doesn't it?
那些讓你看不透的人
When you can't figure a person out.
-尤其是你喜歡的  -天啊  你說什么呢
- Especially when you're attracted. - Oh, my God, what are you...
我和克萊爾·安德伍德沒有私情
I am not involved with Claire Underwood.
我說的是安奈特
I'm talking about Annette.
我現在和任何人都沒有戀愛關系
I'm not involved with anyone at the moment.
每次看見你們兩個在一起  都讓我想起往事
Every time I see the both of you together, it brings back memories.
真沒想到你也會從幕后走上前臺
Never thought you'd step out from behind the scenes.
只要我能為國出力就行  議員
Well, wherever I can do the most good, Congressman.
他可真是一點都沒變
He hasn't changed. Not at all.
是好事  也是壞事
Blessing and a curse.
你為我做的一切  我都沒忘
I haven't forgotten everything you did for me.
不管有我沒我  你都成功進了眾議院
Oh, you made it to the House with or without me.
是你帶我上的道
You showed me the way.
那么
Well...
我一直想來打個招呼
I've been meaning to say hello,
自從你脫黨加入對方之后
ever since you left the party and went to the other side.
簡
Jane.
得有十多年沒和他說話了
Haven't spoken to him in over a decade.
他知道了
He knows.
他知道我參與其中了
He knows I was involved.
難道你沒有嗎
Well, weren't you?
你我都有啊
Weren't we?
你上次去我家是什么時候
When's the last time you were in my house?
別
Don't.
馬克  我不會再去了
Mark, I'm not going back there.
不是
No, no,
和湯姆·耶茨有私情的是新任新聞發言人
Tom Yates was sleeping with the new press secretary
就在白宮里
in the White House.
他拿東部換西部
He traded the East for the West.
是  所有近海油氣開采  先生
Yes, all offshore oil and gas exploration, sir.
他們說我們仍可以進入
They're saying we'll still have access,
但所有通過地中海的航運都會受影響
but all shipping through the Mediterranean will be affected.
而且無法否認  我們將得看他們的臉色
And there's no denying we'll be somewhat at their mercy.
因為根本沒時間請示您
Because there wasn't time to consult you.
佩特羅夫加了碼
Petrov upped the ante
似乎副總統要讓步了
and it looks like the vice president is going to cave.
這個問題不難回答  斯圖爾特小姐
It's not a complicated question, Miss Stewart.
你有沒有和他上床
Were you sleeping with him?
難道還要我說
Do I need to say
本屆政府是在你身上賭了一把嗎
this administration has taken a huge chance on you?
-你們到底有沒有  -跟你沒關系
- Were you sleeping... - It is none of your business.
那就不言自明了
That answers that, then.
這種事正是白宮需要...
This is exactly the kind of thing the White House needs...
避免的
to avoid.
湯姆·耶茨又失蹤了
And Tom Yates is missing.
只會讓整件事情變得更加可疑
Which only makes the whole story more problematic.
我完全不知道這些流言是哪來的
I have no idea where any of this is coming from.
那我建議你否認的方式更有說服力一些
Well, I suggest you find a more convincing way of denying it.
因為你最大的弱點就是不會撒謊  是不是
Because your inability to lie is a liability, right?
我們的總統又在哪呢
Now, where is our president?
你怎么不告訴他們是我邀請你來的呢
Why didn't you tell them I invited you?
你沒有出賣我
You didn't rat me out.
你這口氣像黑幫  總統女士
You sound like a gangster, Madam President.
大概是好奇吧
Curiosity, I suppose.
我想看看你怎么做
I wanted to watch you
聽聽他們怎么說
and hear them.
你的副總統主子太多
Your vice president is serving too many masters.
很奇怪吧
Strange, hmm?
弗蘭西斯剛走  凱茜也走了
Cathy passing away so soon after Francis.
俗話說  死人成三
Death usually comes in threes.
直到又死了第四個  第五個
Except when it comes in fours or fives.
你現在自由了嗎  總統女士
Are you free now, Madam President?
還沒有
Not quite.
他們的提案  你滿意嗎
Were you happy with what they proposed?
我主要是好奇
Mostly, I'm just curious.
好奇什么
About what?
好奇你有什么提議  所以你才邀請我來吧
What you're about to offer. That is why you invited me.
所以我才應邀前來
And that is why I said yes.
奈克西斯安保公司
Well, Nexis Securities
或任何與謝潑德無限責任公司有關的承包商
or any other contractor connected to Shepherd Unlimited
在我任內都將被禁止進入敘利亞
will never be allowed in Syria while I'm president.
這個手段很強硬啊
That's a strong declaration.
有關投標將經過我的批準
Bids will be contingent on my approval.
油氣和港口可以都歸你
You can have the oil and gas, the ports.
以及轉運資源利潤的20%
And 20% of profits from the resources passing through.
這
That's...
還真是慷慨啊
That's quite a taste.
沒準你真是黑幫呢
Maybe you are a gangster.
那么你打算
And how will you...
怎么為自己的立場辯護呢
defend your position?
和平
Peace.
咱們兩個國家這一百年來
Isn't that what our two countries
不是一直以此為借口來開脫
have used to justify what we've done
我們在那個地區做的事嗎
in the region for over a hundred years?
和平言過其實了  克萊爾
Peace is overrated, Claire.
我的副總統的承諾也是一樣
So are my vice president's promises.
但你的開價似乎太大方了
And yet, yours seem too generous.
你丈夫肯定會被這一天的
Your husband would have lost himself
榮耀沖昏了頭
in the brightness of this day,
被他追求的形象蒙住了眼
blinded by how he needed to be seen.
這總讓他代價慘重
That always cost him.
容我問下
Can I ask?
既然你已經知道了
If you knew this...
為什么還要嫁給他
why did you marry him?
你真的知道嗎
Do you even know?
后來才發現
As it turns out...
我丈夫也只是實現目的的手段而已
my husband was a means to an end.
告訴你主子  我不會作證了
Tell the people you work for that I'm not going to testify.
等等
A second.
賽斯
Seth.
賽斯  你聽見了嗎
Seth, do you hear me?
走開吧  道格
Back off, Doug.
不管你告訴他們什么  都跟我無關
Whatever you told them, I'll have no part of it.
聯邦檢察官可以給我發傳票  她可以...
The U.S. Attorney can subpoena me. She can try to...
我不干了
I'm done.
你真是不識好歹啊
You wouldn't know a good thing if it smacked you in the face.
我都不知道我為什么要幫你
I don't know why I'm trying to help you.
你已經不在白宮了  道格
You're not in the White House anymore, Doug.
你去哪了
Where were you?
總統也有三急的  馬克
Even presidents need to pee, Mark.
最近有一些流言
Look, there's a rumor flying around.
-是好事嗎  -很容易打消
- Was it good? - It's easily dismissible.
我還和國安局談了談  沒用的  克萊爾
Then I talked to NSA. It's not gonna work, Claire.
白宮緋聞解決不了這件事的
Some White House affair is not gonna make it go away.
死去的人并不會徹底死去  馬克
The dead never really stay dead, Mark.
他們會活在愛他們的人心中
Not for the people who loved them.
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
你又長高了嗎
Did you get taller?
是啊
Yes.
真奇怪
So strange
有拿破侖情結[矮子更暴力]的人居然會長高
for someone trapped in a Napoleon complex.
可惜你的個性和外表不相稱  簡·戴維斯
If only your personality matched your looks, Jane Davis.
我實在是沒想到  你居然會把談判
I was surprised you left negotiations
交給你的代理  西格森小姐
to your surrogate Ms. Siegerson.
自己的意見還是自己來說比較好
Always best to speak for oneself.
你還有臉說我
That's rich, coming from you.
說一套做一套簡直是你的母語
Doublespeak is your mother tongue.
那巧言詭辯便是你的母語了
And subterfuge is yours.
你和你的那些機構
You and your agencies, hmm?
中情局不過就是文化恐怖分子
The CIA is nothing short of a cultural terrorist.
你這樣的人
It's men like you...
闖進自己一無所知的國家
Barging into countries you know nothing about.
-你真是讓我受不了  -亂中取利
- You get under my skin. - Profiting from destabilization.
留下的只有一片廢墟
Leaving nothing but ruin in your wake.
-簡直是毒藥  -結果你們還生氣了
- It's chemical, it's... - And then you're offended...
你們生氣的是  是我的軍隊  我的空襲
You're offended when it's my men, my air strikes,
-恢復了秩序  -毒藥
- that bring some kind of order. - Chemical!
你就是一個穿著定制西裝的共產黨
You are nothing but a communist in a handmade suit.
一頭豬
A pig!
這么情緒化
So emotional.
情緒化可談不成事的  簡
Emotions make deals come apart, Jane.
告訴我
Tell me,
我憑什么要相信你參與的交易
why should I trust any deal that involves you?
我將不眠不休
I will not rest
直到把你扳倒  維克多
until you're done, Viktor.
直到你死
Dead and buried.
-混蛋  -那...
- Bastard! - Then I guess...
你就熬著吧
you'll never rest.
好了  我的指令很明確
Okay. My directions were clear.
-當然  -那你還有哪里不懂的
- No doubt. - So where's the confusion?
大概是不太明白什么事是你希望發生的
Well, I'm guessing somewhere between what you wanted to happen
什么事是必須發生的吧
and what had to happen.
如果你不希望我打給比爾
If you didn't want me to call Bill,
那你就不該給我聯系他的理由
you shouldn't have given me a reason to.
你根本沒資格參與談判
There was no place for you in that room.
除非你給我足夠的尊重
And unless you show some proper respect,
否則我讓你滾出華盛頓
no place for you in this whole fucking town.
我會親自確保這一點
I'll see to that personally.
我記住了
I'll keep that in mind.
從現在起  乖乖待著  閉上嘴巴
From now on, stay in your lane, keep your mouth shut,
除非我讓你開口  聽見了嗎
unless I say otherwise. You got it?
再說一遍  聽得很清楚
Again, coming in clear,
但我才不在乎
but not a dent.
沒關系  我們會處好的
It's okay, we'll get there.
就算處不來  我有什么好在乎的
Even if we don't, fuck do I care?
我又不為你工作
I don't work for you.
我和你都是他的人
We both work for him.
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper.
我們一般只在精心安排的場合才見面
We usually meet under more orchestrated circumstances.
當然  這次也算是精心安排了
Not that this isn't one of those, as well.
你最近都在忙些什么
Where do you find yourself these days?
為一位很有上進心的眾議員做顧問
Consulting for an ambitious Congressman.
中期選舉要到了
Midterms are coming.
我想
I bet...
他肯定不知道你對黑暗多么適應吧
he has no idea how well you see in the dark.
你最怕的是誰
Who do you fear most?
在所有人中
Out of all of them.
她
Her.
這種場合  我也吃不下去
I can't eat at these things, either.
餐點做得非常好看
The spread looks lovely. Everything.
你們真是盡心了
You all did right by her.
我什么都沒做
Well, I didn't do a thing.
都是斯坦安排的
Stan took care of all of it.
你還好嗎
How you holding up?
我就是想不通
I can't make sense of it.
我父親也是這么走的
My dad went the same way, you know?
一輩子沒生過病  結果
Never sick a day in his life. And then...
正開著車呢就走了
Right when he was driving,
-車子歪到了對向車道上  -天啊
- just drifted onto oncoming traffic. - Jesus.
-我的天  -我還得趕緊抓住方向盤
- Oh, my goodness. - I had to quickly grab the wheel
把車拐到路邊上
and swerved us over to the shoulder.
你那時多大
How old were you?
12歲
Twelve.
12歲  挺難過的吧
Twelve. That's rough.
幾歲不難過呢
It's all rough.
12歲  21歲
Twelve. Twenty-one.
51歲
Fifty-one.
你不可能準備好的
You're never ready.
周三下午她打電話給我
Wednesday afternoon she calls me, as she does.
說她頭疼
Said her head hurt.
好像是偏頭疼厲害了  所以她
Like migraine bad, so she...
要去見她的私人醫生
was headed to her personal doctor.
我回電過去問她的情況
I call back to see how she was doing.
斯坦就告訴我了
Stan hits me with it.
她連辦公室都沒撐到  人在車里就沒了
She didn't even make it to the office. It happened in the car.
所以我就搭最早的飛機過來了
So, I got on the first flight out.
沒事的
Hey, it's okay.
道格說得對
Doug's right.
哭出來吧
It's fine, let it out.
飛機降落時  就全都安排完了
By the time I landed, it was all done.
遺體也
Body was...
就是送去...
whatever, at the place...
火化了
to get cremated.
也沒做尸檢  什么都沒有
No autopsy, nothing.
斯坦做得急匆匆的
Stan made it happen so fast.
只有我控制不住情緒
And I'm the only one who can't keep shit together.
但我就是
But it's just...
連最后一面都沒見著
I never got the chance to see her.
都沒來得及告別
To say goodbye.
實在抱歉  讓你們見笑了
I'm sorry. You all didn't ask for any of this.
-不會的  -我們理解
- No. Please. - We get it.
是  道格·斯坦普和總統似乎很合拍
Yes, Doug Stamper and the President seem very much in sync.
我本想出席國務卿的追悼會
I was hoping to attend the secretary's memorial as well,
但我的時間太緊
but my time is limited.
你遠道而來就已經意義重大了
It was meaningful that you traveled all this way.
你說的話  我一直在考慮
I've been thinking about what you said to me.
我接受
I accept.
我真是太高興了
I'm so happy to hear that.
還有  湯姆·耶茨
One other thing. Tom Yates.
他的事  都是你政府做的
Your government was behind whatever happened to him.
做總統就不能有人性
Presidents aren't allowed to be human.
你必須得選  要權力  還是愛
You have to choose. Power or love.
選哪個從一開始就非常明顯了
That was very clear from the beginning.
原諒我吧  湯姆·耶茨
Forgive me, Tom Yates.
我就要極盡污蔑你
I'm about to drag you through the mud
否認你我之間的感情
to deny we ever happened.
我要再次殺死你
I'm killing you for the second time.
總有一天  你會安息的
One day, you'll rest in peace.
總統女士
Madam President.
女士  有件事我要告訴您
Ma'am, I have to tell you
-最近有一些流言  -我知道
- there are rumors circulating... - I know, I know.
如果您需要我辭職
If you need me to resign...
凱爾茜  你什么都不用做
Kelsey, you're not going anywhere.
愿意的話就去我那  待多久都行
You can stay at my place as long as you like.
太感謝了
I appreciate it.
在貝爾波特待了半個月
Two weeks in Bellport
我可是山窮水盡了
tapped me out.
你們報社可以補助一些啊
Well, your paper will cover some of that.
他們可沒報銷這回事  湯姆
They don't do expenses, Tom.
而且我媽錢也不多了
And my mom didn't have much to leave.
我喜歡這篇文章
I liked the piece.
很有力
It was strong.
打算怎么跟進
What's your follow-up?
環保署又沒人能證實
Well, it's not like anybody at the EPA can confirm.
既然郵件是真的  那就肯定有人收到了
Well, if the emails exist, they went to somebody.
是  可我唯一的消息源不接電話
Yeah, but my only source won't return my calls.
他每天還得上班
He's gotta show up to work every day.
他害怕  也該害怕
He's afraid. He should be.
不如就從應用入手吧
Follow up with the app.
格雷森在場  慫恿驚魂未定的人們注冊
Grayson was there, signing up people who were very scared.
他們利用了危機
They took advantage of a crisis.
-謝潑德家族  -不道德  但也不違法
- The Shepherds. - It's unethical, but it's not illegal.
該死
Oh, shit.
賓夕法尼亞大道封路了
They shut down Pennsylvania Avenue.
這上面說走馬薩諸塞大道
It says to take Massachusetts.
好
All right.
今天是凱茜·杜蘭特的追悼會
It's Cathy Durant's memorial today.
死的人越來越多了
The bodies are adding up.
湯姆  一開始我們以為這么做是正確的
Tom, from the very beginning, we did what we thought was right.
至少當時是正確的
At the time, anyway.
所以我們才都淪落到這輛車里了嗎
Is that how we ended up in this car together?
你不能怨你自己
Look, you cannot blame yourself for...
怨我做得還不夠嗎  為什么不呢
For not doing enough. Why not?
我為什么不怨自己
Why shouldn't I?
瑞秋·波斯納
Rachel Posner?
有人頂著她的名頭
Somebody with her name
在新墨西哥到處消費
is bouncing checks in and around New Mexico.
是  如果什么都查不出來呢
Yeah. And if it leads to nowhere?
你以后有沒有可能
Will you ever be able to...
放棄
leave it?
如果事實越來越查不清楚的話
If the truth starts to fade away?
說實話
Truthfully...
我也不知道
I don't know.
布加耶夫聯系我了  20%
I just heard from Bugayev. 20%?
我還沒告訴馬克和其他人
I haven't told Mark and the rest yet.
你肯定會成眾矢之的的
Just know you'll be crucified.
和我現在的處境有什么不同嗎
Yes, and how will I feel the difference?
你不應該把我排除在外
You shouldn't have excluded me.
你和克萊爾是怎么回事
What's going on with you and Claire?
我只能假設  你入院期間
Look, I can only assume while you were away
有人替你解釋過什么叫瘋狂
somebody broke down the definition of insanity.
如果沒有  那我提醒提醒你
If not, here's a refresher.
瘋狂就是一遍遍重復同樣的蠢事
Doing the same shit over and over
期望著會有不同的結果
and expecting different results.
我不知道她究竟對你說了什么
Yeah, I don't know what she told you
會引發這么嚴重的失憶癥
to induce such amnesia,
但如果你真的還想走上那條路的話
but if you're seriously looking down that road again,
那關于弗蘭西斯的遺囑  有件事你應該知道
there is something that you should know about Francis' will.
她告訴你遺囑里寫什么了嗎
Has she told you what's in it?
誰告訴你的
Who told you?
換了是我  就不會問這個問題
If I were you, that's not the question I'd be asking right now.
我會問  "她為什么不告訴我真相"
I'd be asking, "Why is she keeping me from the truth?"
他留給你的可不止兩個袖扣
He left you more than those cuff links.
不客氣  道格
You're welcome, Doug.
安德伍德總統
President Underwood,
我是布雷特·科爾
Brett Cole.
我認識你
Yes, I know who you are.
我就當這是褒揚了
I'll take that as a compliment.
總統女士  您應該上臺了
Madam President, you should make your way to the stage.
好的  謝謝你
Yes, of course. Thank you.
道格
Doug.
-有空談談吧  -好的  女士
- Speak soon? - Yes, ma'am.
你有什么需要告訴我的嗎
Anything you need to tell me now?
沒什么  沒有
Nope, nothing.
你父親的那個故事  是真的嗎
That story about your father, is that true?
有關系嗎
Does it matter?
如果是真的  那說明了很多
Well, if it's true, it explains a lot.
如果是假的  也說明了很多
If it's not, it explains a lot.
-謝謝您能來  -節哀順變
- Thank you for coming. - Sorry.
謝謝
I appreciate it.
請節哀順變
So sorry.
見到你很高興
Good to see you.
三十年兢兢業業  在險惡的外交戰場
To weather the slings and arrows of 30 years of service
她那標志性的堅強和正直  卻不失分毫
and not lose a fraction of one's signature grit and integrity,
這已經不只是一份遺產
that's not a legacy,
更是一個奇跡
that's a miracle.
凱瑟琳·杜蘭特不只是一位國務卿
But Catherine Durant wasn't just a Secretary of State.
更是我的姐妹
She was a sister.
為什么還沒有人去家里
Why isn't someone on the house right now?
那你聽錯了
Well, then you heard wrong.
沒錯  全天候
That's right. Day and night.
沒錯  每分每秒
Yes, every second
直到他搭C130飛到瑞士
until he is on the C-130 to Switzerland.
不行不行  不要預計
No, no, no. No ETAs.
把日期時間說準了
Hard dates and times.
沒錯
Correct.
不
No.
我親自去安納西接他
I'll be the one to intercept him in Annecy.
好  好的
Yes, of course.
錢一匯過來  我就付給你
As soon as the money is wired, you'll be taken care of.
自特朗普在2016年大選中意外擊敗希拉里
成為美國史上最大的政治黑馬后  希拉里所在的民主黨
就一直指責特朗普團隊在競選期間
暗中勾結俄羅斯  破壞大選的公正性
特朗普2017年炒掉聯調局局長科米后  司法部成立了"專案組"
任命前聯調局局長穆勒為獨立檢察官  領導對"通俄門"指控的調查
經過一年多的調查  穆勒及其團隊已經對17個人進行了正式的起訴
包括俄羅斯網絡黑客  前特朗普競選團隊成員  以及前競選組織主席
另外紐約州的司法部還對特朗普的私人律師進行了起訴
過去一年里  穆勒團隊的主要策略是以輕罪起訴被調查的嫌疑人
想靠給這些人施壓  來換取他們的合作
讓他們供出一些特朗普的猛料來換取自身的自由
同時穆勒還在爭取直接詢問特朗普的機會
數月來一直在同白宮特朗普的律師團商談相關的詢問具體方式和時間
而支持特朗普的一些司法評論人士一直警告特朗普不能輕易上鉤
因為在接受特別檢察官詢問時  稍有不慎  很容易被定下個"妨礙司法"罪
當年比爾·克林頓總統同白宮實習生有染的丑聞被曝光后
并不是因為"生活問題"
而是因為接受大陪審團詢問時"妨礙司法"而被彈劾
目前美國媒體認為
在11月初的中期選舉之后  穆勒的調查將進入收尾階段
屆時專案組是否會對特朗普進行起訴  將會成為全球媒體關注的焦點
而既然民主黨已在中期選舉中奪回了眾議院控制權
即使穆勒的調查結論
無法確定特朗普競選團隊是否同俄羅斯有暗中交易
民主黨仍很有可能會尋找機會啟動彈劾特朗普的程序